These were expensive and he'll grow out of them...
这些非常昂贵 我知道他很快就穿不下…
...in 20 minutes, but I couldn't resist!
但是我就是无法抗拒！
Look at these.
看看这些！
Hey,Ben.
嗨，班
"Just do it"!
做了就对！ （耐吉广告词）
Oh,my God!
喔，天啊！
Was that too much pressure for him?
是不是对他压力太大？
-ls he hungry already? -I guess so.
他已经饿了吗？ 我想是的
You know,it's....
你知道，那个…
Something funny about sneakers. I'll be right back.
球鞋真的很有趣 我马上就回来！
I gotta get one too.
我也要一个
Hey,what are you guys doing?
你们在干什么？
We're just hanging out by the spoons.
我们只是来看看汤匙
Ladle?
要调羹吗？
Will you guys grow up?
你们成熟一点好吗？
This is the most beautiful thing in the world.
这是世上最自然美丽的
Yeah,we know. But there's a baby sucking on it.
我们知道 但现在有个婴儿在吸它
This is my son having lunch,okay? It'll happen a lot,so get used to it.
这是我儿子在吃午餐 你们最好习惯
If you're uncomfortable, just ask questions.
如果你们感到不自在 发问就好
Carol's fine with it.
卡萝不介意的
Carol?
卡萝？
I'm wondering,could Joey ask you a question about breast-feeding?
我想问问乔伊能不能提出 关于哺乳的问题？
Sure.
当然可以
Does it hurt?
会不会痛？
It did at first,but not anymore.
刚开始会，现在不会了
Chandler?
钱德？
So,how often can you do it?
你能多久喂一次？
As much as he needs.
只要他需要就可以
Okay,I got one,I got one.
我想到了一个问题
If he blows into one, does the other one get bigger?
如果他对一个吹气 另一个会不会变大？
The One With the Breast Milk
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第02集 母乳
-Any muffins left? -Yeah,I forget which ones.
还有松糕吗？ 还有，我忘记是哪一种
You're busy,I'll get it.
你太忙了，我来拿
-Anyone else want one? -No,thanks.
谁还要？ 不用，谢谢
You're losing your apron. Let me get it.
你的围裙松了，我帮你系好
-There you go. -Thank you.
好了 谢谢
What a bitch!
真是个恶婆娘！
I have a friend at Bloomingdale's who's quitting...
我有朋友在布明岱尔百货上班 明天就不干了
...and he wants to abuse his discount.
他想要花掉他的折扣优待
Anyone want to come take advantage of it?
谁想跟我去检便宜？
I have to take my grandmother to the vet.
我不行 我要带我祖母去看兽医
-I'll go with you. -Great.
我跟你去 好极了
-Hi,honey. -Hey,sweetums.
嗨，甜心 嗨，蜜糖
And hello to the rest.
哈罗，各位
You can't go shopping with her. What about Rachel?
你不能跟她去逛百货 瑞秋怎么办？
Will it be a problem?
会有问题，对不对？
You're going to Bloomingdale's with Julie.
你要跟茱莉去布明岱尔
It's like cheating on Rachel in her house of worship.
就像是到瑞秋家中偷汉子！
Monica,she will kill you.
她会宰了你
She will kill you like a dog in the street!
她会宰了你 就像宰街上的流浪狗！
So Jules tells me you guys are going shopping tomorrow.
茱莉说你们明天要去逛街
It's actually not that big a deal.
其实没有什么…
It's a big deal to me. This is great.
对我很重要，非常重要
I really appreciate this.
我非常感激你这么做
You're welcome.
别客气
Bijan for men?
碧而泉男性香水？
-Hey,Annabel. -Hey,Joey.
嗨，安娜贝 嗨，乔伊
Did you hear about the new guy?
听说过新来的人吗？
Nobody knows his name. Me and the girls call him "The Hombre Man. "
没人知道他的名字 我们女生都叫他“原野奇侠”
Hombre?
原野奇侠？
What's he doing in my section?
他到我这一区干什么？
I guess he doesn't know.
我想他不知道
Well,he's gonna.
他必须知道
I'll see you a little later,okay?
待会见
Hey,how you doing?
你好吗？
Mornin'.
早
Listen,I know you're new...
听着，我知道你是新来的…
... but it's understood that everything...
但众所皆知这附近的一切…
...from young men's to the escalator is my territory.
从年轻人部门到电梯… 都是我的地盘
"Your territory"?
你的地盘？
-Bijan for men? -No,thanks.
碧而泉男性香水？ 不，谢了
Hombre?
原野奇侠？
Yeah,all right.
好啊
You were saying?
你刚才说什么？
Phoebe,listen. You were with me, and we were shopping all day.
菲比，听着，你跟我一起 逛了整天街买东西
We shopped and we had lunch.
我们买东西，吃午餐
What did I have?
我吃了什么？
-You had a salad. -No wonder I don't feel full.
你吃了沙拉 难怪我觉得饿
Hi. What's up?
嗨，怎么样？
I went shopping with Monica and I had a salad.
我整天都跟摩妮卡买东西 吃了一客沙拉
Good,Pheebs. What'd you buy?
很好，菲比 你们买了什么？
We went shopping for....
我们去买了…
For....
嗯…
For fur.
买了皮毛
You went shopping for fur?
你去买皮毛？
And then I realized that l'm against that.
然后我发现我反对买皮毛
So then we bought some....
于是我们买了一些…
Boobs.
波霸
You bought boobs?
你买了波霸？
Bras!
胸罩！
We bought bras!
我们买了胸罩！
We bought bras.
我们买了胸罩
Bijan for men?
碧而泉男性香水？
Bijan for....
碧而泉…
Hey,Annabel.
嗨，安娜贝
I was wondering if after work we could grab a cup of coffee?
下班后我们可以喝个咖啡吗？
Actually,I sort of have plans.
我已经有计划了
You ready,Annabel?
准备好了吗，安娜贝？
You bet.
好了
Maybe some other time.
以后再约吧
It's not the first time I lost a girl to a cowboy spraying cologne.
我又不是没被喷香水的牛仔 抢走女孩子过
Bijan for men?
碧而泉男性香水？
Bijan for men!
碧而泉男性香水！
And this is Funny Clown.
这是滑稽小丑
It's only for after his naps, not before,or he won't sleep.
只有睡过午觉才可以给他玩 否则他会睡不着
We've been through this before. We have a good time.
我带过他，我们玩得很高兴
We laugh,we play. It's like we're father and son.
我们又笑又玩 就像父亲跟儿子一样
Honey,relax. Ross is great with him.
甜心，放轻松 罗斯很会带他
Don't look so surprised. I'm a lovely person.
别这么惊讶 我是个很好的人
This is so cute!
好可爱！
I got that for him!
我为他买的！
"My Mommies Love Me. "
“我的妈妈们爱我”
That's clever.
真聪明
Oh,hi,Jul....
嗨，茱…
Hi,Jew!
嗨，犹太人！
Okay,sure.
好的，可以
That'd be great. See you then. Bye.
很好，待会见
Did you just say," Hi,Jew"?
你刚才是不是说： 嗨，犹太人？
Yes,I did.
对，我是这么说
That was my friend Eddie Moskowitz.
那是我的犹太朋友 艾迪莫斯考维兹
Yeah,he likes it. Reaffirms his faith.
他很喜欢这称呼 能加强他的信仰
Ben,dinner!
班，吃晚餐了！
Thanks,Aunt Pheebs.
谢谢，菲比姑妈
Did you microwave that? You can't do that to breast milk.
你没有用微波炉吧？ 不应该这样处理母乳
I think I know how to heat breast milk.
我想我知道如何加热母乳
What did you just do?
你在干什么？
I licked my arm,what?
我舔了我的手臂，怎么样？
It's breast milk!
那是母乳！
So?
又怎么样？
Phoebe,that is juice squeezed from a person.
菲比 那是从另一个人身上挤出的汁
What is the big deal?
有什么了不起？
What did you just do?
你又在干什么？
Can people stop drinking the breast milk?
大家能不能不要喝母乳？
You won't even taste it?
你连尝都不尝？
Not even if you just pretend it's milk?
不能假装那是牛奶吗？
Not even if Carol's breast had a picture of a missing child on it.
就算卡萝的乳房 帖了牛奶寻人广告都不行！
-Where is everybody? -At the park. Where have you been?
大家到哪里去了？ 带班去公园了，你去哪里了？
Just out.
出去
Had some lunch. Just me. A little quality time with me.
吃了午餐，只有我一个人 与自己共度美好时光
-Thanks for your jacket. -No problem.
谢谢你的外套 别客气
You can borrow it,by the way.
你也可以向我借
Here are your keys,honey.
这是你的钥匙
If you were at lunch alone, how come it cost you $53?
如果你一个人吃午餐 怎么会要五十三块？
You know what probably happened?
你知道大概发生什么事吗？
Someone stole my credit card.
一定有人偷了我的信用卡
And put the receipt back in your pocket?
然后把收据放回你口袋？
That is an excellent, excellent question.
这是个非常好的问题
That is excellent.
真的非常好
What's with you? Who did you have lunch with?
你怎么了？ 跟谁吃午餐？
-Judy. -Who?
茱蒂 谁？
-Julie. -What?
茱莉 什么？
Jody.
裘迪
You were with Julie?
你跟茱莉在一起？
When it started,I was just trying to be nice to her...
刚开始我只是想对她友善点…
... because she was my brother's girlfriend.
因为她是我哥哥的女友
And then one thing led to another...
然后事情接着发生…
...and before I knew it,we were...
我还不清楚，我们就…
...shopping.
去瞎拼了
Oh,my God!
我的天！
Wait,we only did it once.
慢着，我们只做了一次
It meant nothing to me!
对我没有任何意义！
Really,I was thinking of you the whole time.
我一直想的是你！
Look,I'm sorry,all right? I never meant for you to find out.
对不起，好吗？ 我不希望你知道的
Oh,please! Please! You wanted to get caught!
拜托！你希望被逮到！
That is not true!
才不是！
So you just happened to leave it in here?
所以你不小心留收据在这里？
Did it ever occur to you that I might just be that stupid?
你有没有想到 我会这么笨？
Okay,I just have to know one thing.
好，我必须知道一件事
Did you go to Bloomingdale's?
你是不是跟她去布明岱尔？
Okay,I just really need to not be with you right now.
我现在不能跟你在一起了
Hi,who's this?
嗨，哪一位？
Hi,Joanne. Is Rachel working? It's Monica.
嗨，琼安，瑞秋在吗？ 我是摩妮卡
Yes,I know I did a horrible thing.
我知道我做了很糟糕的事
Joanne,it's not as simple as all that.
琼安，事情没这么简单
No,I don't care what Steve thinks. Hi,Steve.
我才不在乎史提夫怎么想 嗨，史提夫
How did we do?
情况如何？
I tasted Ben's milk and Ross freaked out.
我尝了班的奶水 罗斯发癫了
I did not freak out.
我没有发癫
-Why'd you freak out? -Because it's breast milk.
你为什么发癫？ 因为那是母乳
It's gross!
很恶心！
My breast milk is gross?
我的奶水很恶心？
This should be fun.
这会很好玩
There's nothing wrong with it.
这没什么不对
I just don't think breast milk is for adults.
我只是不认为 母乳是给大人喝的
Of course,the packaging does appeal to grownups and kids.
当然母乳的容器 很吸引大人与小孩
Don't be silly. I've tried it. It's no big deal.
别傻了，我试过，没什么
Just taste it.
尝一尝
That would be no.
不行
-Come on. -Try it.
来嘛 尝一尝
It's natural.
很自然
It doesn't taste bad.
又不难吃
Yeah,it tastes kind of sweet. Sort of like....
有一点甜，很像…
Like what?
像什么？
Cantaloupe juice.
哈密瓜汁
Exactly.
没错
You've tasted it.
你尝过了
Oh,you've tasted it.
喔，你尝过了
You can keep saying it, but it won't stop being true.
你可以一直说下去 也不会变成假话
Give me the bottle.
把奶瓶给我
Get me the towel.
把毛巾给我
Howdy.
吃饱没？
Give me a box of juice.
给我一罐果汁
Well,they switched me over to Hombre.
他们把我调到原野奇侠了
Maybe it's because of the way you're dressed.
也许是因为你的穿着
Or this guy's doing so good they want to put more people on it.
或因为那砘锉硐痔好了 他们要增加人手
This guy goes through two bottles a day now.
那砘镆惶煊玫袅狡
What do you care?
你在乎什么？
You're an actor. This is your day job. It's nothing!
你是个演员 这只是你的副业，没什么
I know,but I was the best.
我知道，但我本来是最棒的
You know? I liked being the best.
我喜欢当最棒的
Maybe I should get out of the game.
也许我应该退出江湖
They need guys up in housewares to serve cheese.
厨具部门需要有人切乳酪
Say you do that.
假如你这么做了
Sooner or later,somebody will come along that slices a better cheddar.
将来迟早有人会出现 乳酪切得比你更好
Then where you gonna run?
那时候你要逃到哪里？
You're right.
也许你说得对
I say you show him what you're made of. Stand your ground.
我说你应该发挥大丈夫气概
Show him that you're the baddest Hombre west of the lingerie!
让他知道你是内衣部西边 最厉害的原野奇侠！
-I'm gonna do it! -All right!
我要这么做！ 好极了
Now,go see Miss Kitty and she'll fix you up with a nice hooker.
现在去找猫咪小姐 她会介绍个好妓女给你
I don't know what to say.
我不知道该说什么
That's good because I'm not listening.
很好，因为我不会听
I feel terrible. I really do.
我觉得很糟糕，真的
I'm sorry. Did my back hurt your knife?
对不起 我的背伤害了你的刀吗？
Say that I'm friends with her. Is that so terrible?
我跟她交朋友，一起去逛街 这有什么不好？
-It's that terrible? -You don't get it!
真的很不好吗？ 是的，你还不懂吗？
It's bad enough she stole the guy...
她偷走我的男人已经够糟了…
...who may be the person l'm supposed to be with.
我可能会跟他长相厮守
But now...
但现在…
...she's actually....
她竟然…
But now she's actually stealing you!
现在她竟然连你也抢走了！
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Nobody could steal me from you.
没人能把我从你那里抢走
Because I'm friends with her doesn't make me any less friends with you.
我与她交朋友 不会影响我与你的感情
You're my....
你是我的…
And we're....
我们是…
-Oh,I love you! -I love you too!
喔，我爱你！ 我也爱你！
You guys,I know that this really doesn't have anything to do with me.
喂，我知道这与我完全无关
But I love you guys too!
但我也爱你们！
I really needed that.
我很需要这样
I know that right now...
我知道现在…
...you really need to hate Julie's guts.
你很想恨死茱莉
But she didn't do anything wrong.
但她没有做什么错事
She's just a girl who met a guy, and now they go out.
她只是认识了一个男生 现在他们在交往
I think that if you gave her a chance,you'd like her.
我想如果你给她一个机会 你会喜欢她的
Will you give it a chance?
你愿意给她一个机会吗？
For me?
为了我？
I'd do anything for you, you know that.
我愿意为你做任何事 你知道的
I'd do anything for you!
我什么都愿意为你做！
Wait,wait,wait!
等一下！
Mornin'.
早
I said,mornin'!
我说：早！
I heard you.
我听见了
All right,everybody. I'm opening the doors.
好，各位 我要开门了
You boys ready?
你们准备好了吗？
Ready.
好了
Yeah,l'm ready.
我也好了
You idiot! You stupid cowboy!
你这个白痴！ 笨牛仔！
You've blinded me! I'm suing!
你弄瞎我了！我要告你们！
Oh,my God! Todd! What the hell did you do?
天啊！陶德！你在搞什么鬼！
Sorry. I'm such a doofus!
对不起，我真是笨手笨脚！
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
对不起，非常对不起
My God,what happened?
老天，发生什么事？
These new kids,they never last.
这些菜鸟，都撑不了很久
Sooner or later they all...
迟早他们就会…
...stop lasting.
…捅出纰漏
What do you say I buy you that cup of coffee now?
我们去喝杯咖啡怎么样？
Sure.
好啊
I just thought we should hang out.
我想我们应该亲近亲近
I mean,you know, we've never really talked.
你知道的 我们从来没有真正谈过话
I guess you'd know that, being one of the two of us.
我想你说得对 因为你是我们两个之一
I know.
我知道
I probably shouldn't even tell you this...
我也许不该告诉你…
... but l'm pretty much totally intimidated by you.
但我实在很怕你
Really?
真的？
Me?
怕我？
Oh,my God,are you kidding?
你在开玩笑吗？
Ross is so crazy about you...
罗斯还是对你很着迷…
...and I really wanted you to like me,and l....
我真的希望你喜欢我
It's probably me just being totally paranoid...
也许我只是胡思乱想…
...but I kind of got the feeling that maybe you don't.
但我好像觉得你不喜欢我
Well,you're not totally paranoid.
你不是完全胡思乱想
When you and Ross first started going out...
当你与罗斯刚开始交往时…
...it was really hard for me...
我真的很难过…
...for many reasons of which l'm not gonna bore you with now.
有太多理由，我不要烦你
I see how happy he is and how good you guys are together.
但我看到他非常快乐 而且你们在一起是多么相配
And Monica's always saying how nice you are...
摩妮卡一直说你有多好…
...and God,I hate it when she's right!
我真讨厌她说得对！
Thanks.
谢谢
Would you like to go to a movie sometime or something?
你想不想一起去看电影 或出去玩？
Yeah,that'd be great. I'd love it.
这样很好，我很乐意
I'd love it too.
我也是
Shoot,I gotta go.
我必须要走了
-So I'll talk to you later. -All right,Julie.
待会见 好，茱莉
What a manipulative bitch.
真是个玩弄人的贱人！
It's not bad.
真不赖